{
    "id": "5271dd6d8f18466887dc389acf453492",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We will get there as soon as you ………………..",
            "description": "In as..as clauses, a present tense is often used to refer to the future.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "will",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Tired ……………………… she was, she went on working.",
            "description": "After an adjective/adverb, both as and though can be used in a special structure.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… it may seem strange, I don’t enjoy watching movies.",
            "description": "As can mean though only when it is used in a special structure after an adjective / adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there ……………………….. water in the pond?",
            "description": "We use any in questions and negatives.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… the paper to the attorney’s office.",
            "description": "Bring is used for movements to the places where the speaker or the hearer is.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "brought",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot help ………………………… what she is going to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but wonder",
                "but wondering",
                "except wonder"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… speak ten languages.",
            "description": "Both can and be able to can be used to talk about ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "is able to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This machine ………………………… be operated by a child.",
            "description": "Be able to is not normally used in passive structures.",
            "answers": [
                "is not able to",
                "cannot",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam was ten times ………………………….. than I expected.",
            "description": "Before than we use a comparative expression.",
            "answers": [
                "as much difficult",
                "more difficult",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am late, ………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "amn't I",
                "am I not",
                "aren't I"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ………………………….",
            "description": "We use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "intelligent",
                "intelligently",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He never lets me ………………………… a sentence.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to after let.",
            "answers": [
                "finish",
                "to finish",
                "finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}